myshop.com.pk 2014-02-09

# Security Policy | Myshop Online

### Privacy Policy

We have designed our website so that you can visit MyShop without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. Once you have chosen to provide us with personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified), you can be assured that it is not displayed online and it is not accessible to the general public. Your personal information will be used solely for the purpose of order processing and personalization only. MyShop strives to have consistent privacy practices for your personal information regardless of the medium used to collect the information. Therefore, this privacy policy applies to all online, offline and manually processed personal information.

↑ Back to Top

### Notice

MyShop provides this online Privacy Policy to make you aware of our privacy practices and of your choices about the way your information is collected and used. We take seriously the trust you place in us. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at the bottom of every web page.

↑ Back to Top

### What we collect

At our online MyShop Store, you can order products or services. When you place an order with us, we collect your contact and billing information so that we may send you an order confirmation, provide you with information regarding your purchase(s) and for the purpose of delivering your product. Please note that financial information (such as credit card numbers and billing address) is NOT required online, since we're not processing credit cards online at the moment. 

MyShop does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and MyShop products and services do not target information to children under 13. MyShop is committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents to take an active role in your child’s online activities and interests.

↑ Back to Top

### How we use the information

MyShop uses your information to help us understand your needs and interests and provide you with better services. We use your information to help you complete a transaction or order, to communicate with you, to provide service and support, to update you on products and benefits and to personalize promotional offers. 

Occasionally, we may also use your information to contact you for market research or to provide you with marketing information we think would be of particular interest. We will always provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us.

↑ Back to Top

### Who we share it with

MyShop Corporation will not sell, rent or lease your personally identifiable information to others. MyShop will not share your personal information with a business partner or any unrelated third-party company unless you give your permission. 

We protect the personal information you share with us. Access to your personal information is limited to authorized personnel. 

MyShop may respond to subpoenas, court order, or legal process. We also may choose to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. MyShop may also collect and share information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of a person, violation of MyShop’ terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

↑ Back to Top

### Choice

MyShop will not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ways described above without offering you a choice. We will also provide you the opportunity to let us know if you wish to opt-out of partial or all contact from MyShop and we will do everything we can to honor such requests. Please contact MyShop for assistance. 

Links to third-party web sites on MyShop sites are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave the MyShop site. MyShop has not reviewed all of these third-party sites, does not control and is not responsible for any of these sites, their content or their privacy policies. Thus, MyShop does not endorse or make any representations about them or any information, software or other products or materials found there or any results that may be obtained from using them. If you decide to access any of the third-party sites linked to this site you do so entirely at your own risk.

↑ Back to Top

### Access & Accuracy

In an effort to keep your personal information accurate, please notify us of changes to your name, address, title, phone number or email address. We have included contact information for MyShop to update your information. We may process or store your information in our MyShop database. 

The most effective way to view, update or remove your information is to log into your account, and update your account information.

↑ Back to Top

### Cookies

While you move through MyShop, we may track your visit through the creation of a "temporary cookie". Cookies is a technology used to customize web site content to better meet your needs by storing and remembering your individual preferences. This enhances your experience by allowing us to deliver content specific to your interests and to recognize you when you return to our site at another time. This is a standard industry practice used on most major web sites. Most browsers are originally configured to accept cookies but you can reset your browser to notify you when you have received a cookie giving you the chance to choose whether to accept it or not. You should understand however, that if you do disable cookies areas of some web sites will not function properly.

↑ Back to Top

### IP Addresses

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our web site. It is not disseminated to other parties for any reason.

↑ Back to Top

### Contact Information

We value your comments and opinions. If you have comments or questions about our privacy policy or need help with your privacy choices please contact us at [info@myshop.com.pk](mailto:info@myshop.com.pk)

↑ Back to Top
